hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Hmm, what?
A wanted flyer.
"This man who calls himself Tokichi
is a major criminal
who has killed a family of three"
"He has a bird-shaped birthmark
on his chest"
A bird-shaped birthmark?
It couldn't be.
What is it, Hinata?
I can't tell because
his face is covered with scars.
But he has... a bird-shaped birthmark.
He has... a bounty on his head, too?
What the heck is going on
with everything?
Catch or be Caught?!
Showdown at
the OK Temple
Where are you going, old man?
Just rest quietly.
Let go.
Stay out of my way. Gosunkugi is mine.
What the heck can you do
in that condition, you wanted man?
A bounty hunter who was in the bar
attacked last night.
What's the idea of a bounty
chasing after a bounty?
It's none of your concern.
Your wound again.
Stop!
Don't move.
I didn't do it.
Then, how do you explain
this wanted flyer?
That Gosunkugi did it.
He killed an innocent family of three...
just to steal money.
What do you mean by that?
I was a swordsmith in a tiny village
in a small country
sandwiched between two large countries.
I was poor,
but for me it was a happy life.
But on that festival day...
I was about to go deliver a sword
that a customer had ordered.
I wanted to participate in the festival,
so I was hurrying.
At that very moment...
For some reason,
the door was half open.
It's Tokichi.
I'm delivering the sword you ordered.
I told everyone everything as it happened.
But the people in the village
wouldn't believe me.
It's because I was the only one
who hadn't shown up at the festival.
And the particular shape of the sword
that stabbed through the family.
A swordsmith should be able to make
any kind of weapon.
That was the reason.
Stand up, Tokichi!
Tokichi! Don't let him get away!
After him!
And ever since...
I've wandered aimlessly
from town to town.
"ONE MILLION RYO"
It was something the villagers had issued.
And there was one more
wanted flyer beside mine...
of the man who killed the family.
I resolved to capture Gosunkugi
with my own hands.
I would clear my name
and return to my village,
And to get some information about him,
if even just a little...
I became a bounty hunter
despite having a price on my own head.
So, that's why we were in the way, huh?
The only way to prove my innocence
is for me to capture him myself.
I want to go home.
Will you concede him to me?
We're Ninja. We carry out missions
we've received, no matter what!
Even if the worst were to happen,
we can't let him get away.
Let's go.
Was that okay, Naruto?
That Gosunkugi jerk!
We have to capture him, no matter what.
That's right.
And if that old man, Sazanami,
pushes it too far in his condition,
not only will he fail
in capturing Gosunkugi,
he could end up getting killed instead.
Don't hold back. I'll give you...
the likes of my head.
You're wounded,
so I can kill you whenever I want.
Before that, I'll be taking Gosunkugi.
Well, I guess I'll just have
those Shinobi kids do their best.
The Land of Stone, Post Station 2.
It seems everything in this town,
politics, economics, military,
is conducted by monks.
It really is. Nothing but temples.
The temple,
which could be called the head temple,
is the OK Temple on that mountain.
Hey, Hinata. What's that bell?
That was created as
the sightseeing crown jewel
to recruit people to live in their temple.
The Golden Bell!
It's just like it is saying,
"Please steal me."
I know. Gosunkugi is after that bell!
— Yeah.
But how does that Gosunkugi guy
intend to steal that bell?
Naruto.
You guys are Gosunkugi's!
Are these guys going to corral us?
Just like the time with Sazanami.
Byakugan.
Look out! Run!
Old Man Sazanami?
Leave this to me.
All right!
Eat this!
What are you doing here?
I just came to settle the score.
But your wound is still...
I won't get in your way.
I'll pursue the target on my own.
This is a competition.
I guess it can't be helped. I accept.
But we can't even start
as things stand now.
There are still nails in the ground.
He's waiting for the best moment.
Gosunkugi!
The bell is at the top!
What? Could it be?
Oh, no!
The nails in the ground aren't moving.
— The Jutsu has worn off!
— What?
Damn it! When did he...?
So, as the words say,
we've been "nailed down," huh?
They're by the bell!
— Why that...
— Wait.
Don't forget the bounty hunter
from last night is also after Gosunkugi!
No problem.
We'll get there first, no matter what.
Let's go!
— How awful.
— That Gosunkugi jerk!
Unforgivable!
Hey! Where's Gosunkugi?
Naruto! He'll get away if we're too slow!
We don't have any time to think.
Let's take care of this in one shot!
Gentle Fist!
Akamaru!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry.
Man-Beast Clone!
Fang Over Fang!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Uzumaki!
Naruto Barrage!
Here I go.
I hit you with the back of the sword.
Where's Gosunkugi?
That way!
— Gosunkugi.
— He's ours!
Old man, you're going to prove
your innocence, right?
If you're a bounty hunter,
then show your pride!
Ninja Art: Flying Nail Mist.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Eat this!
Too slow!
Farewell.
Damn it!
It's not over yet!
— What?
— Prepare yourself!
Wait!
Don't be hasty.
If I kill you, the one who can prove
my innocence will be gone.
We lose.
That's right.
What?!
Bounty Sazanami,
otherwise known as Tokichi...
I, Gatsu, have apprehended you!
And you, bounty Gosunkugi!
Your spree of evil deeds...
The number of charges against you
is incalculable.
A government official has ordered
you hauled in for questioning.
Old man...
Damn it. There's nothing we can do
if the opposition is a bureaucrat.
You murderer!
Give back the family you killed!
We'll kill you in the same way!
Damn it!
Hey, hey, you guys! You've got
some nerve putting up wanted flyers
without a thorough investigation!
This man is the true culprit behind
the murder that occurred in this village!
WANTED REWARD THREE MILLION RYO
Gosunkugi has already been apprehended
and has confessed.
And the weapon has been seized.
Therefore, this individual, Tokichi,
shall be acquitted!
You jerks!
You made me work for free!
What are you going to do about it?
Why'd you do that for me?
I overheard some stupid tale of woe,
you see.
It makes no difference
to a bounty hunter...
but I overheard it,
and so I had no choice.
It was necessary to verify whether or not
you really are a wanted man.
You.
Not "you" Gatsu.
I'm also a bounty hunter.
I'm in the same trade as you.
Gatsu
Tokichi, we're sorry.
Forgive us, Tokichi.
Good for you, old man Sazanami.
Let's go.
I've kind of gotten homesick
and really miss the Leaf Village.
But, you know,
a failed mission means failure.
The Fifth Hokage's going
to scold you good, Naruto.
What?!
You failed another mission?!
I... don't want to go home.
dokomademo tsudzuku michi ni wa ironna koto arunda ne
so many things happen on this endless road, right?
tsuyogari na kimi ga kyou wa juwaki koshi ni namida koe
although you're strong-willed your voice wavered on the phone today
donna yume oikakete kokomade kitan darou
what dreams did you chase to get here?
wakara na kunattari suru koto wa boku ni datte aru kara nee BABY
even I have times when I just don't understand baby
kimi ga namida no toki ni wa boku ga soba ni iru kara
when you're sad I'll be close to you
hanareba nare no yoru datte boku wa soba ni iru kara
even on nights when we're apart I'll be close to you
boku wa soba ni iru kara
I'll be close to you
Creeping up noisily, a round, fat guy and a skinny one!
Beneath the scorching rain, a disastrous tranquility ensues.
Tsunade hits the jackpot!
Kakashi's guess is a huge bust!
Heard it somewhere, this unprecedented event!
The great acts of Monday and Pocha!
Then comes Naruto...
Let me join in the training too!
Next time:
"Meeting the Rare Visitors. A Great Beast? Wild Beats...? Rare Beast?"